<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<Section xmlns="urn:com.io7m.structural:8:0"
         title="Overview">
  
  <Subsection title="Introduction">
    <Paragraph>
      The <Term type="package">exfilac</Term> application is a simple application that aims to do one thing well: Get
      data out of Android devices and into <LinkExternal target="https://aws.amazon.com/s3/">S3</LinkExternal> buckets.
    </Paragraph>
  </Subsection>

  <Subsection title="Features">
    <Paragraph>
      The <Term type="package">exfilac</Term> application provides the following features:
    </Paragraph>
    <FormalItem title="Features">
      <ListUnordered>
        <Item>
          The application can work with any S3-compatible storage provider. This includes
          <LinkExternal target="https://aws.amazon.com/s3/">Amazon AWS</LinkExternal>,
          <LinkExternal target="https://docs.vultr.com/vultr-object-storage">Vultr Object Storage</LinkExternal>,
          <LinkExternal target="https://www.idrive.com/s3-storage-e2/">IDrive®</LinkExternal>, and many other
          commercial offerings. Additionally, the application can work with self-hosted S3 storage solutions such
          as <LinkExternal target="https://min.io/">MinIO</LinkExternal>.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          The application can (recursively) upload the contents of any directory on an Android device to which it has 
          been granted access. The set of directories is configurable.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          The application conserves precious bandwidth by avoiding uploading files that already exist on the remote 
          storage. The cryptographic hashes of files are computed locally and files are only uploaded if the hashes of 
          the files on the remote server do not match.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          The application can be configured to upload files on a timed schedule, and/or in response to various
          events occurring on the device such as a photo being taken, or the network becoming available.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          The application vigorously respects the privacy of users: The application contains no telemetry or analytics
          of any kind, and never collects any user data.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          Development of the application is performed in the open. The complete source code is made available under
          an extremely liberal <LinkExternal target="https://opensource.org/license/isc-license-txt">ISC</LinkExternal>
          license, and development and bug tracking is handled in a public
          <LinkExternal target="https://www.github.com/io7m-com/exfilac">GitHub</LinkExternal> repository.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          The application rejects bug-prone Android programming practices and libraries and instead strives for
          correctness and stability using battle-hardened, well-tested components designed outside the traditional
          Android ecosystem.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          The application adopts a cautious development approach and does not pursue huge sets of complex features. The
          application attempts to adhere to the
          <LinkExternal target="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unix_philosophy">Unix philosophy</LinkExternal> and
          provide a simple, sharp tool that does one thing well.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          The application attempts to respect the intelligence of users. Technical details of many aspects of the
          system are clearly displayed onscreen, and important information is not hidden in the misguided pursuit of
          "user-friendliness".
        </Item>
        <Item>
          The application is comprehensively documented; you are currently reading this documentation!
        </Item>
      </ListUnordered>
    </FormalItem>
  </Subsection>
  
</Section>
