<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<Section xmlns="urn:com.io7m.structural:8:0"
         id="6f66cea7-9131-42ad-9bfc-98a2d9676bc2"
         title="Privacy Policy">

  <Subsection title="Overview">
    <Paragraph>
      This privacy notice tells you what to expect us to do with your personal information.
    </Paragraph>
  </Subsection>

  <Subsection title="Contact Details">
    <Paragraph>
      Email:
      <Term type="constant">exfilac-privacy@io7m.com</Term>
    </Paragraph>
  </Subsection>

  <Subsection title="What Information We Collect, Use, and Why">
    <Paragraph>
      We do not collect any personal information. The application currently keeps the following information internally:
    </Paragraph>
    <FormalItem title="Internal Data">
      <ListUnordered>
        <Item>
          A 30-day rotating set of internal debug logs. These never leave the device unless the user specifically
          downloads them from the device and sends them to us for problem reporting.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          A 7-day log of the most recent upload operations. These never leave the device.
        </Item>
      </ListUnordered>
    </FormalItem>
  </Subsection>

  <Subsection title="Lawful Bases and Data Protection Rights">
    <Paragraph>
      Under UK data protection law, we must have a "lawful basis" for collecting and using your personal information.
      There is a list of possible lawful bases in the UK GDPR. You can find out more about lawful bases on the ICO's
      website.
    </Paragraph>
    <Paragraph>
      Which lawful basis we rely on may affect your data protection rights which are in brief set out below. You can
      find out more about your data protection rights and the exemptions which may apply on the ICO's website:
    </Paragraph>
    <FormalItem title="Lawful Bases">
      <ListUnordered>
        <Item>
          Your right of access - You have the right to ask us for copies of your personal information. You can request
          other information such as details about where we get personal information from and who we share personal
          information with. There are some exemptions which means you may not receive all the information you ask for.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          Your right to rectification - You have the right to ask us to correct or delete personal information you think
          is inaccurate or incomplete.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          Your right to erasure - You have the right to ask us to delete your personal information.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          Your right to restriction of processing - You have the right to ask us to limit how we can use your personal
          information.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          Your right to object to processing - You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          Your right to data portability - You have the right to ask that we transfer the personal information you gave
          us to another organisation, or to you.
        </Item>
        <Item>
          Your right to withdraw consent – When we use consent as our lawful basis you have the right to withdraw your
          consent at any time.
        </Item>
      </ListUnordered>
    </FormalItem>
    <Paragraph>
      If you make a request, we must respond to you without undue delay and in any event within one month. To make a
      data protection rights request, please contact us using the contact details at the top of this privacy notice.
    </Paragraph>
  </Subsection>

  <Subsection title="Our Lawful Bases For The Collection And Use Of Your Data">
    <Paragraph>
      Consent - we have permission from you after we gave you all the relevant information. All of your data protection
      rights may apply, except the right to object. To be clear, you do have the right to withdraw your consent at any
      time.
    </Paragraph>
  </Subsection>

  <Subsection title="Where We Get Personal Information From">
    <Paragraph>
      We don't collect any personal information.
    </Paragraph>
  </Subsection>

  <Subsection title="How Long We Keep Information">
    <Paragraph>
      If a user submits log files as part of a problem report, the log files are deleted as soon as the problem has been
      fixed.
    </Paragraph>
  </Subsection>

  <Subsection title="How To Complain">
    <Paragraph>
      If you have any concerns about our use of your personal data, you can make a complaint to us using the contact
      details at the top of this privacy notice.
    </Paragraph>
    <Paragraph>
      If you remain unhappy with how we've used your data after raising a complaint with us, you can also complain to
      the ICO.
    </Paragraph>
    <Paragraph>
      The ICO's address:
    </Paragraph>
    <FormalItem title="ICO Address">
      <Verbatim><![CDATA[
Information Commissioner's Office
Wycliffe House
Water Lane
Wilmslow
Cheshire
SK9 5AF

Helpline number: 0303 123 1113

Website: https://www.ico.org.uk/make-a-complaint
]]></Verbatim>
    </FormalItem>
  </Subsection>

  <Subsection title="Last Updated">
    <Paragraph>
      <Term type="constant">2024-09-16</Term>
    </Paragraph>
  </Subsection>

</Section>
