<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<Section xmlns="urn:com.io7m.structural:8:0"
         title="Tutorial">

  <Section title="What You Need To Know First">
    <Paragraph>
      In order to start using the application, you'll need to know a few details first:
    </Paragraph>
    <FormalItem title="Prerequisites">
      <ListUnordered>
        <Item>
          You'll need to know the configuration details of one or more <Term type="term">S3 buckets</Term> that you'll
          be using to receive data. Configuring an S3 bucket on a server is outside the scope of this documentation and
          is, in any case, very provider-specific. Assuming that you have created an S3 bucket on a server, you'll need
          to know the following:
          <ListUnordered>
            <Item>
              The bucket <Link target="847c0c85-9eb2-4cca-8ec2-6a6752d9239a">name</Link>.
            </Item>
            <Item>
              The bucket <Link target="693185cf-f0eb-4a9d-9881-226dac7196fa">access key</Link>.
            </Item>
            <Item>
              The bucket <Link target="3cb22d3a-2373-470d-bc9c-a56d59ff5941">secret key</Link>.
            </Item>
            <Item>
              The bucket <Link target="9e930051-3999-44c3-9f29-f45344f313f4">region</Link>.
            </Item>
            <Item>
              The bucket <Link target="0e1e653a-1a95-4013-a3b5-ee432c480b63">endpoint</Link>.
            </Item>
          </ListUnordered>
        </Item>
        <Item>
          If you want to use <Link target="391252b2-ee7f-4157-97a5-98d5dd5ee2f6">QR code configuration</Link>, you'll
          need to know how to use QR encoding tools. The
          <LinkExternal target="https://github.com/sorairolake/qrtool">qrtool</LinkExternal>
          package comes highly recommended.
        </Item>
      </ListUnordered>
    </FormalItem>
  </Section>

  <Section title="Buckets"
           id="bdf8b20e-f5f7-41a1-ba41-e6dc6b799f13">
    <Subsection title="Overview"
                id="589c3df0-2a73-4dd7-a95f-57aa684d36c0">
      <Paragraph>
        The application opens to a set of tabs. The initially visible tab is the
        <Term type="term">Buckets</Term>
        tab. This is, unsurprisingly, where you'll configure the S3 buckets to which you want to upload files. The
        buttons in the toolbar allow for configuring an S3 bucket
        <Link target="161ae260-7a37-444c-95de-65198fae2369">manually</Link>
        or, alternatively, configuring an S3 bucket from a
        <Link target="391252b2-ee7f-4157-97a5-98d5dd5ee2f6">QR code</Link>.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Buckets">
        <Image source="screen_buckets.png"
               type="screenImage">
          The "buckets" screen.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Manual Configuration"
                id="161ae260-7a37-444c-95de-65198fae2369">
      <Paragraph>
        Clicking the <Term type="term">Create Bucket</Term> toolbar button opens a screen that allows for configuring
        the details of an S3 bucket manually.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Buckets">
        <Image source="screen_create_bucket.png"
               type="screenImage">
          The "create bucket" screen.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
      <Paragraph id="70486361-f260-4806-b847-4ae6cd0db5d8">
        The <Term type="term">Reference Name</Term> field holds the name that you'll use to refer to the bucket in other
        parts of the application. This name can be anything, although there are some restrictions on the characters that
        are allowed to be used in the name. Don't worry; the UI will tell you if a name is valid or not as you type each
        character. The name can't be changed later, so try to pick something useful and descriptive.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph id="847c0c85-9eb2-4cca-8ec2-6a6752d9239a">
        The <Term type="term">Name</Term> field holds the actual name of the S3 bucket as it appears on the server.
        Amazon S3 in particular has
        <LinkExternal target="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/userguide/bucketnamingrules.html">
          a long list of restrictions on the names of buckets</LinkExternal>.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph id="9e930051-3999-44c3-9f29-f45344f313f4">
        The <Term type="term">Region</Term> field holds the region within this bucket resides. For self-hosted options
        such as <LinkExternal target="https://min.io/">MinIO</LinkExternal>, the region will always be
        <Term type="constant">us-east-1</Term>.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph id="693185cf-f0eb-4a9d-9881-226dac7196fa">
        The <Term type="term">Access Key</Term> field holds the access key that will be used to access the bucket. You
        can think of an access key as being analogous to a username in other systems. Typically, this will either be a
        username, or it'll be an
        <LinkExternal target="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles.html">IAM role</LinkExternal>
        and will look like a short string of random alphanumeric characters.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph id="3cb22d3a-2373-470d-bc9c-a56d59ff5941">
        The <Term type="term">Secret Key</Term> field holds the secret key that will be used to access the bucket. You
        can think of a secret key as being analogous to a password in other systems.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph id="6c5bc851-c576-4ba8-b788-c776c2021e1d">
        The <Term type="term">Access Style</Term> menu declares the method by which the bucket will be accessed. This
        option is slightly esoteric, and the value you select will depend on which S3 storage provider you're using on
        the server side. On Amazon AWS, at the time of writing, Amazon are recommending that people use
        <LinkExternal target="https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/userguide/VirtualHosting.html">
          virtual host
        </LinkExternal>
        style access. In <Term type="term">virtual host</Term> mode, you would specify the
        <Link target="0e1e653a-1a95-4013-a3b5-ee432c480b63">endpoint</Link>
        of the server as, for example,
        <Term type="constant">https://s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com</Term>. Then, for a bucket named
        <Term type="term">example-23</Term>, the S3 client would actually make requests to the address
        <Term type="constant">https://example-23.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com</Term>
        behind the scenes.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        In contrast, for <Term type="term">path style</Term> access, the name of the bucket is simply added at the end
        of the <Term type="term">endpoint</Term> URL. In <Term type="term">path style</Term> mode, you would specify the
        <Link target="0e1e653a-1a95-4013-a3b5-ee432c480b63">endpoint</Link>
        of the server as, for example,
        <Term type="constant">https://s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com</Term>. Then, for a bucket named
        <Term type="term">example-23</Term>, the S3 client would actually make requests to the address
        <Term type="constant">https://s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com/example-23</Term>
        behind the scenes.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        Systems such as <Term type="package">MinIO</Term> require the use of
        <Term type="term">path style</Term>
        access. Amazon AWS currently accepts either access style in practice. Consult your S3 provider's documentation
        for the rules.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph id="0e1e653a-1a95-4013-a3b5-ee432c480b63">
        Finally, the <Term type="term">Endpoint</Term> field specifies the actual base address that will be used for the
        S3 bucket. If you're hosting S3 buckets yourself using <Term type="package">MinIO</Term>, then this is simply
        the address of the server. If you're hosting S3 buckets on AWS, then this will be an address such
        as <Term type="constant">https://s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com</Term>. Again, you'll need to consult your S3
        provider's documentation for the right server endpoint to use.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Buckets">
        <Image source="screen_create_bucket_filled.png"
               type="screenImage">
          The "create bucket" screen, configured.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
      <Paragraph>
        Once you've configured all the fields, and none of the fields are showing a red warning icon, you can click the
        <Term type="term">Save Bucket</Term>
        button in the toolbar to save the bucket. Don't worry if you realize you got some of the details wrong; you can
        <Link target="5452065f-2a70-4c8c-9915-95d91b4d4423">modify buckets</Link>
        at any time. Once you have at least one bucket defined, you can proceed to the
        <Link target="025bbd03-a513-4272-b486-8c4d0c06d844">uploads tab</Link>.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>

    <Subsection title="QR Code Configuration"
                id="391252b2-ee7f-4157-97a5-98d5dd5ee2f6">
      <Paragraph>
        Entering long strings of characters using on-screen keyboards can be painful. To alleviate some of that pain,
        it's possible to use third-party tools to put configuration information into a
        <LinkExternal target="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/QR_code">QR code</LinkExternal>, and then have the
        application scan the QR code to automatically configure a bucket.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        Data in the QR code must be in the
        <LinkExternal target="https://docs.oracle.com/en/java/javase/21/docs/api/java.base/java/util/Properties.html">
          Java properties
        </LinkExternal>
        format. This is a simple line-based format where each line specifies a
        <Term type="term">key</Term>
        and a <Term type="term">value</Term>, separated by either a colon or an equals symbol. Key names are
        case-sensitive.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        For example, a valid configuration in this format might look like this:
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Example Configuration"
                  id="3a4be325-1eab-49e3-bff7-2ee5a3d3eb36">
        <Verbatim><![CDATA[
AccessKey=fc87a046
AccessStyle=PATH_STYLE
Bucket=tablet-test
Endpoint=https://s3.example.com
Name=qrtest
Region=us-west-1
SecretKey=03cbe0c80539c8bb2883c2f3bb239f62cab89493
]]></Verbatim>
      </FormalItem>
      <Paragraph>
        When given to a QR encoding tool, the following image will be produced:
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Example Configuration (QR)"
                  id="9aa8e6f6-f7ac-4136-86ec-613673b55ed2">
        <Image source="qrcode.png">
          Example configuration QR code.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
      <Paragraph>
        This table lists the keys and their meanings:
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Configuration Property Keys"
                  id="9a9695e7-a7b9-49fd-b773-3318e4aed44b">
        <Table type="genericTable">
          <Columns>
            <Column>Key</Column>
            <Column>Meaning</Column>
          </Columns>
          <Row>
            <Cell>AccessKey</Cell>
            <Cell>The bucket access key.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>AccessStyle</Cell>
            <Cell>The bucket access style. Must be
              <Term type="constant">PATH_STYLE</Term>
              or
              <Term type="constant">VIRTUALHOST_STYLE</Term>.
            </Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Bucket</Cell>
            <Cell>The name of the bucket on the server.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Endpoint</Cell>
            <Cell>The server endpoint.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Name</Cell>
            <Cell>The bucket's reference name.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Region</Cell>
            <Cell>The bucket region.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>SecretKey</Cell>
            <Cell>The bucket secret key.</Cell>
          </Row>
        </Table>
      </FormalItem>
      <Paragraph>
        Upon clicking the <Term type="term">Create Bucket (from QR code)</Term> toolbar button, the device's camera will
        open and you will be given an opportunity to scan a QR code. Assuming the QR code is correctly scanned, the
        <Link target="161ae260-7a37-444c-95de-65198fae2369">bucket configuration</Link>
        screen will open, and you'll be given a chance to review and/or modify the parsed configuration values.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        In practical terms, none of the keys listed above are required to be present in the QR code. If a key is
        missing, you will simply have to enter the corresponding value manually on the bucket configuration screen after
        scanning.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        Once you have at least one bucket defined, you can proceed to the
        <Link target="025bbd03-a513-4272-b486-8c4d0c06d844">uploads tab</Link>.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>

    <Subsection title="Modify Buckets"
                id="5452065f-2a70-4c8c-9915-95d91b4d4423">
      <Paragraph>
        Clicking a bucket in the bucket list will take you back to the
        <Link target="161ae260-7a37-444c-95de-65198fae2369">manual configuration</Link>
        screen and allow you to change the details for a bucket.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Bucket Modification">
        <Image source="screen_buckets_modify.png"
               type="screenImage">
          Bucket modification.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Delete Buckets"
                id="70a759b6-0d0e-48f6-89b3-43013fc50460">
      <Paragraph>
        Clicking the checkbox on the right hand side of a bucket selects that bucket for deletion. With one or more
        buckets selected, a <Term type="term">Delete Bucket</Term> button becomes accessible in the toolbar. Clicking
        the <Term type="term">Delete Bucket</Term> button asks for confirmation and then deletes the selected buckets.
        Note that, if a bucket is deleted, any
        <Link target="025bbd03-a513-4272-b486-8c4d0c06d844">uploads</Link>
        associated with the bucket will also be deleted.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Bucket Deletion">
        <Image source="screen_buckets_delete.png"
               type="screenImage">
          Bucket deletion.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
    </Subsection>
  </Section>

  <Section title="Uploads"
           id="025bbd03-a513-4272-b486-8c4d0c06d844">
    <Subsection title="Overview"
                id="3791ebc0-31b9-4c0f-b782-3510a0cdecfe">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Uploads</Term> tab is where you'll tell the application about the data you want to upload.
        If the <Link target="bdf8b20e-f5f7-41a1-ba41-e6dc6b799f13">Buckets</Link> tab is considered to describe
        <Term type="term">where</Term>
        the data will end up, then the <Term type="term">Uploads</Term> tab can be considered to describe
        <Term type="term">what</Term>
        data is uploaded to any given bucket, and
        <Term type="term">when</Term>
        exactly those uploads occur.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Uploads">
        <Image source="screen_uploads.png"
               type="screenImage">
          The "uploads" screen.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Configuration"
                id="9b1a6603-a4e7-465a-9ce8-46040e168b10">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Create Upload</Term> button in the toolbar opens a configuration screen to allow for
        defining new uploads.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Uploads">
        <Image source="screen_create_upload.png"
               type="screenImage">
          The "create upload" screen.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
      <Paragraph id="d43ac35e-f04d-4b69-9a5d-8dad3e1f57e9">
        In a similar manner to <Link target="70486361-f260-4806-b847-4ae6cd0db5d8">bucket reference names</Link>, the <Term type="term">
        Upload Name
      </Term> field holds the name you'll use to refer to the upload in other parts of the application. This name can be
        anything, although there are some restrictions on the characters that are allowed to be used in the name. Don't
        worry; the UI will tell you if a name is valid or not as you type each character. The name can't be changed
        later, so try to pick something useful and descriptive.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph id="fe9422bc-2685-420c-8fba-5031cba7efb4">
        The <Term type="term">Device Directory</Term> field holds the name of the directory that will be scanned for
        files for this upload. Unfortunately, Android has been steadily moving towards restricting access to the device
        filesystem for years. It's therefore likely to be much easier to use the
        <Term type="term">Select Directory</Term>
        button to choose a directory on the device than to try to manually enter a path that Android will actually
        accept. The
        <Link target="18647abb-0b23-49d7-93b9-a71021c6a9ce">implementation</Link>
        section of this manual has details on the generally user-hostile configuration that Android now provides.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph id="50250af7-d6b4-496b-ba5e-1a3eb76e3641">
        The <Term type="term">Schedule</Term> menu allows for selecting how frequently an upload will be attempted,
        assuming that no other events trigger it into running. The menu allows for one of the following values:
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Schedules"
                  id="7ec370a3-cfc9-4049-8e3e-0994d0ee816a">
        <Table type="genericTable">
          <Columns>
            <Column>Value</Column>
            <Column>Meaning</Column>
          </Columns>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Every five minutes.</Cell>
            <Cell>The upload will be attempted every five minutes.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Every ten minutes.</Cell>
            <Cell>The upload will be attempted every ten minutes.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Every twenty minutes.</Cell>
            <Cell>The upload will be attempted every twenty minutes.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Every thirty minutes.</Cell>
            <Cell>The upload will be attempted every thirty minutes.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Every hour.</Cell>
            <Cell>The upload will be attempted every sixty minutes.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>No schedule; only upload on trigger events.</Cell>
            <Cell>
              The upload will not use a time-based schedule and will only start in response to one or more of the
              configured <Link target="64e72ee1-3f96-4ce7-9c7d-cff74ec09dde">trigger events</Link> having occurred.
            </Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>No schedule; only upload manually.</Cell>
            <Cell>
              The upload will not use a time-based schedule and will only start if you manually trigger it.
            </Cell>
          </Row>
        </Table>
      </FormalItem>
      <Paragraph id="4e07294b-5ec6-45bd-b53d-5ced70d32841">
        The <Term type="term">Bucket</Term> menu allows for selecting a bucket to which to upload. The values in the
        menu correspond to the <Link target="70486361-f260-4806-b847-4ae6cd0db5d8">reference names</Link> of any buckets
        you have configured.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph id="64e72ee1-3f96-4ce7-9c7d-cff74ec09dde">
        The various switches in the <Term type="term">Triggers</Term> section specify events that will cause the upload
        to start running. The currently supported trigger events include:
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Triggers"
                  id="2c736c6f-cce9-41df-89d8-b57f96b5b348">
        <Table type="genericTable">
          <Columns>
            <Column>Value</Column>
            <Column>Meaning</Column>
          </Columns>
          <Row>
            <Cell>
              A photo was taken.
            </Cell>
            <Cell>
              The upload will start when a photo is taken. This can be useful for ensuring that photos taken on the
              device camera are promptly sent to the server.
            </Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>
              The network became available.
            </Cell>
            <Cell>
              The upload will start when the network moves from a state that is considered "unavailable" to a state that
              is considered "available". The precise meaning of this is described in the
              <Link target="f6482692-5b3e-42ec-a3f5-17a85fbb7c1b">implementation section</Link>
              of this manual.
            </Cell>
          </Row>
        </Table>
      </FormalItem>
      <Paragraph>
        Once you've configured all the fields, and none of the fields are showing a red warning icon, you can click the
        <Term type="term">Save Upload</Term>
        button in the toolbar to save the upload. Don't worry if you realize you got some of the details wrong; you can
        <Link target="b93f7d36-e82d-4b5b-9b00-bee7701e841c">modify uploads</Link>
        at any time. Once you have at least one upload defined, you can proceed to the
        <Link target="24b84a43-be73-415c-89ef-bd3219ce7d41">status tab</Link>.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>

    <Subsection title="Modify Uploads"
                id="b93f7d36-e82d-4b5b-9b00-bee7701e841c">
      <Paragraph>
        In a similar manner to <Link target="5452065f-2a70-4c8c-9915-95d91b4d4423">bucket modification</Link>, clicking
        an upload in the upload list will take you back to the
        <Link target="9b1a6603-a4e7-465a-9ce8-46040e168b10">configuration</Link>
        screen and allow you to change the details for an upload.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>

    <Subsection title="Delete Uploads"
                id="1b74a8d9-6dd9-4475-96b7-e95a0f48ee22">
      <Paragraph>
        In a similar manner to <Link target="70a759b6-0d0e-48f6-89b3-43013fc50460">bucket deletion</Link>, clicking the
        checkbox on the right hand side of an upload selects that upload for deletion. With one or more uploads
        selected, a <Term type="term">Delete Upload</Term> button becomes accessible in the toolbar. Clicking the <Term type="term">
        Delete Upload
      </Term> button asks for confirmation and then deletes the selected uploads.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>
  </Section>

  <Section title="Status"
           id="24b84a43-be73-415c-89ef-bd3219ce7d41">
    <Subsection title="Overview"
                id="d1748852-edcf-4704-8db2-cce3f75f27b3">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Status</Term> tab shows the current status of every defined upload. The
        <Term type="term">Start/Stop Upload</Term>
        button allows for manually starting uploads, or cancelling uploads that are currently running. Clicking on an
        item in the status list will open a
        <Link target="d1fda434-5f2b-4ada-8f47-724b02034a4e">details</Link>
        screen for the most recent execution of an upload.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Status">
        <Image source="screen_status.png"
               type="screenImage">
          The "status" screen.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Details"
                id="d1fda434-5f2b-4ada-8f47-724b02034a4e">
      <Paragraph>
        The details screen for a given upload shows information about the most recent execution of an upload.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Status Details">
        <Image source="screen_status_details.png"
               type="screenImage">
          The "status details" screen.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
      <Paragraph>
        The details page displays the following fields:
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Fields"
                  id="a64f26a9-a2fb-4dfd-a142-1b9b6bacd9b0">
        <Table type="genericTable">
          <Columns>
            <Column>Field</Column>
            <Column>Meaning</Column>
          </Columns>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Upload ID</Cell>
            <Cell>The unique execution ID of the upload. Each execution of an upload will be assigned a new ID.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Bucket</Cell>
            <Cell>The reference name of the bucket to which data is being uploaded.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Reason</Cell>
            <Cell>The reason the upload started.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Time Started</Cell>
            <Cell>The time and date the upload started.</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Time Ended</Cell>
            <Cell>The time and date the upload ended (assuming that it has ended).</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Duration</Cell>
            <Cell>The total duration of the upload (assuming that it has ended).</Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Files (Required)</Cell>
            <Cell>
              The number of files that were discovered by the most recent scan of the directory associated with the
              upload.
            </Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Files (Skipped)</Cell>
            <Cell>
              The number of files that were skipped because it was determined that they had already been fully uploaded
              by a previous upload attempt, and their contents had not changed since then.
            </Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Files (Failed)</Cell>
            <Cell>
              The number of files that failed to be uploaded due to some kind of error.
            </Cell>
          </Row>
          <Row>
            <Cell>Files (Uploaded)</Cell>
            <Cell>
              The number of files that were successfully uploaded during this upload execution. It is normal for this
              value to be zero if no files have been created or changed since the last execution of this upload.
            </Cell>
          </Row>
        </Table>
      </FormalItem>
    </Subsection>
  </Section>

  <Section title="Settings"
           id="fbafb6f9-10fe-4d3e-8726-6b091d16a207">
    <Subsection title="Overview"
                id="5592193b-8a5a-4354-ae5f-e539761c8483">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Settings</Term> tab shows the global settings for the application.
      </Paragraph>
      <FormalItem title="Settings">
        <Image source="screen_settings.png"
               type="screenImage">
          The "settings" screen.
        </Image>
      </FormalItem>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Networking">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Networking</Term> section of the settings screen controls how the application will
        handle the general aspects of networking on mobile devices.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Allow uploads on cellular connections</Term> option, if enabled, will allow uploads
        to occur if the device's networking is being provided by some kind of cellular connection. This option is
        disabled by default, as the use of these kinds of networks can be financially costly for some users.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Allow uploads on Wi-Fi</Term> option, if enabled, will allow uploads
        to occur if the device's networking is being provided by Wi-Fi. This option is
        enabled by default.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Upload">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Upload</Term> section of the settings screen provides general settings that affect
        all uploads.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Pause uploads</Term> option, if enabled, will prevent all uploads from executing until
        the control is disabled. Note that uploads that are currently in progress will not be cancelled.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="User Manual">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">User Manual</Term> option will open the user manual in a web browser.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Support">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Support</Term> option will open a web browser and take you to a location where you
        may be able to get technical support for the application.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Privacy Policy">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Support</Term> option will open the application's privacy policy in a web browser.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Commit">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Commit</Term> option shows the unique identifier of the source code
        <LinkExternal target="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Commit_(version_control)">commit</LinkExternal>
        that was used to build the application.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>
    <Subsection title="Version">
      <Paragraph>
        The <Term type="term">Version</Term> option shows the current application version number.
      </Paragraph>
    </Subsection>
  </Section>

</Section>
